(Howard:)We don't pray to them.
We prey on them.
(Raj:)Whatever, dude. The point is
Leonard's got one and you don't.
(Sheldon:)Is this it?
(Sheldon:)It was inappropriate to discuss Leonard
and Penny's sex life...
(Sheldon:)...in front of Leonard and Penny.
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Now I can eat.
[INSECT CHIRPING]
(Raj:)-What's that?
-Sounds like a cricket.
(Sheldon:)Hang on.
(Sheldon:)Based on the number of chirps
per minute and the temperature...
(Sheldon:)...it is a snowy tree cricket.
Oh. Give me a fricking break.
How could you possibly know that?
(Sheldon:)In 1890, Emile Dolbear determined
there was a fixed relationship...
(Sheldon:)...between the number of chirps per
minute and the ambient temperature.
(Sheldon:)A precise relationship that is not present
with ordinary field crickets.
How do you know the temperature
of this room?